http://www.janszenloudspeaker.com/pages/privacy

TECHNOLOGY
What makes electrostatics better?
What makes JansZen electrostatics better?
TECHNOLOGY
What makes electrostatics better?
What makes JansZen electrostatics better?
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://janszenaudio.com and Janszen Loudspeaker, Ltd. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Janszen Loudspeaker, Ltd. include https://janszenaudio.com and JansZen Audio. The JansZen Audio website is a ecommerce site. By using the JansZen Audio website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, JansZen Audio may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
-         First and Last Name
-          Mailing Address
-          E-mail Address
-          Phone Number
If you purchase JansZen Audio's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
JansZen Audio collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
JansZen Audio may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from JansZen Audio and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
JansZen Audio does not and will not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
JansZen Audio may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. JansZen Audio may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to JansZen Audio, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
JansZen Audio may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on JansZen Audio or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of JansZen Audio; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of JansZen Audio, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
JansZen Audio may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within JansZen Audio, in order to determine what JansZen Audio services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within JansZen Audio to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by JansZen Audio. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the JansZen Audio website.
Use of Cookies
The JansZen Audio website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize JansZen Audio pages, or register with JansZen Audio site or services, a cookie helps JansZen Audio to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same JansZen Audio website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the JansZen Audio features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the JansZen Audio services or websites you visit.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security of your Personal Information
JansZen Audio secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. JansZen Audio uses the following methods for this purpose:
-          SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
JansZen Audio does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe from Third Party Communications
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from third-party partners of JansZen Audio by contacting us here:
- Web page: https://janszenaudio/opt-out
- Email: opt-out@janszenaudio.com
- Phone: (614) 448-1811
E-mail Communications
From time to time, JansZen Audio may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from JansZen Audio or click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from JansZen Audio, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on UNSUBSCRIBE button.
Changes to this Statement
JansZen Audio reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
JansZen Audio welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that JansZen Audio has not adhered to this Statement, please contact JansZen Audio at:
Janszen Loudspeaker, Ltd.
480 Trade Rd.
Columbus, Ohio 43204
Email Address:
sales@janszenloudspeaker.com
Telephone number:
Sign up for articles by David Janszen about audio, plus the latest on new developments, show reports, and more…
© 2020 JansZenAudio.
Sign up for articles by David Janszen about audio, plus the latest on new developments, show reports, and more…
Original script code:
